personalbrandingblog.com 2015-12-26

# Privacy Policy | Personal Branding Blog - Stand Out In Your Career

### 

###   
What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or email address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the ‘do we use cookies?’ section below for our information about cookies and how we use them.

* * *

### **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience. Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
  * To improve our website. We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * To improve customer service. Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * To process transactions. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering purchased product or service requested.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To send periodic emails.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you may.

* * *

### **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information will not be stored on our servers.

* * *

### **Do we use cookies?**

yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

###   

* * *

### **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outisde parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

* * *

### **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have seperate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity or our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

* * *

### **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the [California Online Privacy Protection Act](http://www.oispp.ca.gov/consumer_privacy/default.asp). We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

* * *

### **Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with requirements of COPPA ([Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act](http://www.ftc.gov/ogc/coppa1.htm), we do not collect any information from anyone 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

* * *

### **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This only privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and sister websites (Personal Branding Magazine, Personal Brand Awards, Personal Branding TV, DanSchawbel.com) and not information collected offline.

* * *

### **Disclaimer**

Please also visit our disclaimer page governing the use of our website

* * *

### **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

* * *

### **Change to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
